<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Identity Data Provider</string>
    <string name="icon" translatable="false">PW\n🆔</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile:</string>
    <string name="recalibrate">Recalibrate</string>
    <string name="error_msg_first_calibration">First calibration is mandatory</string>
    <string name="checkbox" translatable="false">✓</string>
    <string name="new_user">New user</string>
    <string name="go_back" translatable="false">◀</string>
    <string name="previous" translatable="false">❮</string>
    <string name="next" translatable="false">❯</string>
    <string name="exit_double_press">Please click BACK again to exit</string>
    <string name="error_wrong_pattern">Wrong pattern!</string>
    <string name="error_new_user_primary_tests">To add new user please complete all primary tests for at least one calibration setting</string>
    <string name="error_custom_pattern_primary_tests">To add custom pattern please complete all primary tests for at least one calibration setting</string>
    <string name="custom_pattern_tap_twice">Tap again to set up custom pattern</string>
    <string name="error_new_pattern_length">Patterns have to be longer than 4</string>
    <string name="info_welcome_header">Welcome</string>
    <string name="info_welcome_content">
        Hi! For starters I\'d like to thank you for your will to help me with my project.
        Note that if you close this window, you can always reopen it by pressing PW🆔 button to the top left.
    </string>
    <string name="info_project_header">Project</string>
    <string name="info_project_content">
        The purpose of this project is to verify if it\'s possible to create and identification layer that uses behavioral information of drawing security patterns.
        Data that you\'re going to provide will be completely anonymous.
        Your unique ID is randomly generated during your first launch of the application and it disappears when the application is uninstalled - each installation will generate a new ID.
        You can view your ID at the bottom of this dialog screen and test it by reinstalling this apk.
    </string>
    <string name="info_instructions_header">Instructions</string>
    <string name="info_instructions_content">
        There are two tasks. Primary and optional. In both you\'ll have to draw patterns on your screen.
        You can treat this like the \'connect the dots\' game.
        In order to make this as easy and comfortable for you as possible, you\'ll first need to adjust the height of the pattern grid.
        To do that you\'ll just have to move your finger up and down and then press check icon.
        Don\'t worry, you can readjust the height after that if you think it\'s too high or too low.
    </string>
    <string name="info_primary_header">Primary task</string>
    <string name="info_primary_content">
        Once the calibration process is finished, you\'ll be tasked to draw 3 primary patterns at least 20 times.
        Remember that number of drawn patterns is specific to your user, pattern and calibration option, so if you readjust the grid height, the counter will be different.
        Don\'t worry about them though, these counters are not reset so you can always switch your settings back and continue on.
    </string>
    <string name="info_optional_header">Optional task</string>
    <string name="info_optional_content">After completing primary task you will unlock optional tasks. There are two ways to do them.
        \n1) You can add new user by pressing your Profile\'s name (\'Default\').
        When you set up a new profile, the calibration setting will also automatically switch back to the option where you completed the most tests.
        Once you set up a new profile, lend your phone to your friend or family member so that they could also complete the primary tests.
        Remember that for them to count to the system, they will have to complete at least 20 tests for at least one pattern.
        The more people provide data for the same phone and calibration setting, the better the results will be.
        \n2) You can add your own custom patterns. If there\'s a pattern that you\'re particularly familiar with, you will be able to add it with no issues.
        In order to add/switch patterns just double tap on the pattern string.
    </string>
    <string name="info_about_header">About</string>
    <string name="info_about_content">
        Creator: Radosław Gryta, Warsaw University of Technology
        \nSource code: github.com/rgryta/IdentityCreator</string>
    <string name="info_uuid_header">Your unique ID</string>
    <string name="close_x" translatable="false">✗</string>
    <string name="right_triangle" translatable="false">▸\t</string>
    <string name="down_triangle" translatable="false">▾\t</string>
    <plurals name="completed_tests">
        <item quantity="other">Completed tests: %d</item>
    </plurals>
</resources>