<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">IdentityCreator</string>
    <string name="icon" translatable="false">PW<br/>🆔</string>
    <string name="info_string">Warsaw University of Technology <br /><br />
        User modeling and identification based on touch and gyro analysis <br />
        Purpose of this project is to verify if it is possible to authenticate current smartphone holder based on the behavioral characteristics of touch input.<br /><br />
        Instructions:<br />
        1. Data acquisition is performed in two ways. Basic tests where you will be asked to recreate predefined patterns multiple times and personalised tests where you will be able to create a new pattern, maybe one you are most comfortable with.<br />
        2. Pattern is a 3x3 grid of points which simulates a screen unlocking system.<br />
        3. On the next page you\'ll be greeted with a calibration screen. Calibration is needed in order to set up the pattern grid in the most comfortable position for the user.<br />
        4. You will be able to recalibrate the screen, but after such action, you\'ll be asked to perform the basic tests once again.<br />
        5. (Optional) You will also be asked to let a different user use your phone in order to perform the same tasks. This will significantly help with the research.<br />
        6. Correct pattern is displayed as a string of numbers starting from 1 and ending at 9, counting from left to right and from top to bottom. For example straight line from top left to top right will be displayed as 1-2-3.<br />
        7. You can revisit this page using INFO button.<br />
        <br /><br />
        Thank you for your contribution to the project. <br />
        by Radoslaw Gryta
    </string>
    <string name="profile">Profile:</string>
    <string name="recalibrate">Recalibrate</string>
    <string name="error_msg_first_calibration">First calibration is mandatory</string>
    <string name="calibration_exists">Calibration option already exists. Updating view…</string>
    <string name="checkbox" translatable="false">✓</string>
    <string name="new_user">New user</string>
    <string name="go_back" translatable="false">◀</string>
    <string name="previous" translatable="false">❮</string>
    <string name="next" translatable="false">❯</string>
    <string name="exit_double_press">Please click BACK again to exit</string>
    <string name="error_wrong_pattern">Wrong pattern!</string>
    <string name="error_new_user_primary_tests">To add new user please complete all primary tests for at least one calibration setting</string>
</resources>